<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Module>
    <ModulePrefs
            title="HideShow"
            author="Justin Kruger"
            author_email="jdavid.net@gmail.com" height="800">
        <Require feature="opensocial-0.9" />
        <Require feature="views" />
        <Require feature="dynamic-height" />
        <Require feature="settitle" />
        <Require feature="osapi" />
        <Optional feature="content-rewrite">
            <Param name="exclude-urls">/.*/</Param>
            <Param name="expires">86400</Param>
        </Optional>
    </ModulePrefs>
    <Content type="html" view="default, all, canvas, canvas.owner, canvas.t, profile, home, preview, update"><![CDATA[<!--HTML-->
    <!-- #includes -->
    <!DOCTYPE html>
    <link rel="stylesheet" href="css/gadget.css" type="text/css" media="screen, projection" >
    
    <script type="text/javascript" src="http://ajax.googleapis.com/ajax/libs/jquery/1.4.2/jquery.js"></script>
    <script type="text/javascript" src="js/os.js" ></script>
    <script type="text/javascript" src="js/UCSF.js"></script>
]]></Content>
<Content type="html" view="home, canvas, canvas.owner, update"><![CDATA[<!--HTML-->
<!-- HideShow -->
<!-- a control that is visible on some views, but not all. -->
<div id="hideshow"></div>
<!-- HideShow end -->
]]></Content>
<Content type="html" view="profile"><![CDATA[<!--HTML-->
<h1>Profile</h1>
<p>
The profile view assumes an anonymous user that is looking at the page owner's profile.
Gadgets, Widgets or Apps on these pages should be small, fast loading summaries of data
related to that app. They should be minimally interactive, and may direct a user to a
Preview, Canvas, Home, or Profile view.
</p>
]]></Content>
<Content type="html" view="home"><![CDATA[<!--HTML-->
<h1>Home</h1>
<p>
The home view, assumes that the owner and viewer are the same, and will load a number of
Apps, Widgets or Gadgets on the same web page. Home views should load quickly and have a
minimal amount of interactivity.  Home views usually direct to a 'full' screen view like
the canvas page for more interactivity, and administration, where there is only one app
loaded on the web page.
</p>
]]></Content>
<Content type="html" view="canvas"><![CDATA[<!--HTML-->
<h1>Canvas</h1>
<p>
A large application view that either the owner or the viewer of the application can see.  
Usually the network requires the veiwer to be a registered and "loged in" user, since most
apps will require access to the api(s) which will either need viewer or owner access.
</p>
<p>
The preview view is more or less meant for users that are not yet logged in or have not 
yet installed the application, and are looking for an exmple of the app before granting access.
</p>
]]></Content>
<Content type="html" view="canvas.owner, update"><![CDATA[<!--HTML-->
<h1>Canvas.owner</h1>
<p>
In many cases for opensocial apps there are things that only make sense in the context of
the viewer being the owner. Using canvas.owner in the UCSF context implies that the app is
in a large format, and that the owner = viewer.  This is great for admin pannels of apps or
for apps that are specifically ment for the context of the user.
</p>
<p>
Because of how primary and secondary names are used, canvas.owner might get a name without a
"dot" notation like "update".
</p>
]]></Content>
<Content type="html" view="preview"><![CDATA[<!--HTML-->
<h1>preview</h1>
<p>
The preview view is more or less meant for users that are not yet logged in or have not 
yet installed the application, and are looking for an exmple of the app before granting access.
</p>
]]></Content>
</Module>